JANELLA SENICA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

I am a full-stack web developer with a professional background in project, revenue, and client management. Throughout my experiences, I discovered how much I enjoy solving problems, analyzing data, and collaborating with teams which led me to the world of coding. I love the challenge and learning something new everyday.

EXPERIENCE

MANAGER

OMNICOM MEDIA GROUP | NOV 2016 - JUL 2019

- Planned, tracked, and executed media campaigns
- Managed \$330M+ of commercial inventory across all media platforms
- Collaborated with Sales Team to create client presentations

SENIOR ANALYST

OMNICOM MEDIA GROUP | JUN 2015 - NOV 2016

- Managed 30+ accounts from inception to completion
- Resolved discrepancies for media campaigns
- Created sales proposals to accomplish clients' budgets and goals while maximizing profit and revenue for OMG

STRATEGIC PLANNING ANALYST | JAN 2013 - JUN 2015

CNN NETWORKS | NOV 2016 - JUL 2019

- Facilitated communication among the Ad Ops, Sales, and Account Management Teams
- Analyzed budgets, actuals, and projections for forecasts

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS, COMMUNICATIONS
TEMPLE UNIVERSITY

CERTIFICATION, FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

THE UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS AT AUSTIN

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript | HTML | CSS | jQuery Bootstrap | Node.js | Express | MySQL | MongoDB

CONTACT
LINKEDIN.COM/IN/JANELLASENICA

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/JAESENIX